MANUEL PORTERO LEIVA





+34 629947930

RPA/Software Developer



manuel.portero.leiva@gmail.com

Personal Profile

Well educated RPA and Software Developer with more than 3 years of experience in Power Platform, Uipath, and Cloud Development. I'm analytical, problem solver and I have good communication skills, especially with people that don't have a technical background. I have experience working in different countries with people from other cultures.

EXPERIENCE

Power Platform / RPA Developer

06/2022 - Present

OMYA Business, Barcelona, ES

Develop, maintain and operate OMYA's robot service. Supplying OMYA's plants and business around the world. My tasks in this role are:

- Coding robots using UiPath and Visual Basic, JavaScript and PowerShell as a language code.
- Build and manage CI/CD operations with Azure Devops.
- Develop auxiliar apps with PowerApps and create auxiliar PowerAutomate flows in order to automate daily team tasks.

Proof of knowledge (Click over image):

UiPath:



PowerApps:



PowerAutomate: 🞵



Power Platform / Cloud Developer

06/2022 - 11/2020

SEIDOR S.A, Barcelona, ES

Working as a consultant for SEIDOR's infrastructure división as a Power Platform, Cloud and RPA developer. As consultant, my tasks in this role were:

- Develop PowerApp applications using FX, Html, CSS, Javascript, React y Jquery.
- Create DPA automations (PowerAutomate) and RPA (Power Automate Desktop) using Artificial Intelligence as complement (Ai-Builder, Cognitive Services).
- Design and develop cloud data provisioning solutions with Azure Automation y Azure Function

Proof of knowledge (Click over image):



PowerApps: PowerAutomate: 📶 A.Function: 🥠 Ai-Builder: 🤫









EDUCATION

Computer Science Bachelor Institut Obert de Catalunya 2023-2019

HNC Web Development Glasgow Kelvin College 2019-2020

Health and Safety Master Ceu San Pablo 2015-2015

Chemical engineering (Bachelor W.H.) Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona 2007 - 2014

COMPL. EDUCATION

Machine Learning Course (150 h) **EU Support Fundings**

2022

PORTFOLIOS

RPA Developer Portfolio

htps://rpa-portfolio.vercel.app/

Full Stack Developer Portfolio

https://full-stack-port-folio.vercel.app/

Industrial IT Portfolio

https://industrial-it-portfolio.app/

Web Developer (Trainee)

06/2019 - 12/2020

Kinning Park Complex, Glasgow Uk

Web development for Kinning Park Complex comunitary center. Administration and mantintain IT equipments. My tasks in this job were:

- Web administration with Wordpress using HTML,Css, Javascript and PHP.
- Install and repair IT equipments.

Web: Weblink

Proof of knowledge (Click over image):

HTML,CSS:



JavaScript(React):



HOBBIES

Arduino/Pi:



3D Printing:



Languages:



SKILLS

Coding

Python, Visual Basic, FX, JavaScript

Automation tools

Power Automate, UiPath, Logic Apps

Cloud development tools

Azure Automation, Azure Functions

Frameworks

NodeJS, Flask, React, Angular

Libraries

UiPrime, Selenium, Beautiful Soup

Database

Azure SQL, Mysql, Postgresql

IA (Low Code)

Cognitive Services, Ai-Builder

CI / CD

Azure Devops

Languages

Spanish, Catalán (Native)

French, Italian (Intermediate)

PROJECTS

Caprolactam's Factory Construction

Project Link

Librería H.Garcia Auditory

Project Link

Social Network (Node)

Project Link

Hotel Network System

Project Link